So we could access the context that you saw here, and it's pretty cool.
Now let's update the state when users sign in or sign up.
All right.
So here the sign in place, you can see we have saved in the local stories now instead of just setting
the async stories.
Let's also use this to the context.
All right.
So for that, we import to use context
and then to start using context, we can use
a youth context.
So we need to restructure state and said state farm use context and we give us context.
Let's make sure we input context as well.
Import of context from.
From context of.
I guess we put our context, we use the context, so that means we should have access to this state.
Now let's save in the Asian stories and let's say.
Let me just put it right here and don't.
Sit.
So in context, so since the dollar helped reduce its spread.
Whatever he's under today in the state and update the user.
Now before we do that, actually we don't have to spend a week in the state data because this state
only content, the user token and here in the response group, that is exactly what we get, user and
domain.
So we can do this directly use instant data.
OK.
It's a dollar and a once use a log log in.
We can even redirect them to home based.
So we can do that.
We should alert and then we can navigate, so we have already distinctive navigation so we can use that
to redirect navigation, dart and navigate.
I would never get to go home soon.
So whatever screen name you have used in your navigation here in the app, whatever name you have used,
the exact same name you use to navigate the use of this code, what it will do this in the sign into
once use a sign, did you save the data and it's in service?
You saved the data in the context and you navigate the user to home base.
Let's do the same in San Pedro.
The first thing you want to invoke use context.
They want to input all context.
Context, let me just say the important point here, that's right to its context, and then to study
using context, we can use use context.
Let's do structure state since to use context.
So we keep on context.
OK, in this fix, then something happened.
OK.
Context, we have that context now, so here let's.
Say two contexts.
Said state data, and then we can redirect the user.
Navigation to navigate through home.
Now, before I try, I want to do one more thing, and that is configuring the excuse.
All right, so let me go to the context.
The reason I want to configure its use is later we need to send the token that we have here.
We rescind this token to our server.
If you want to access some protected routes, maybe to create a new post and delete new, delete your
post that then we need to apply the authentication in the server so that then we have to send this token
in the excuse how this is done.
So to avoid that.
In this config excuse, you get this from the local stores and put in the excuse headers so that it
will send automatically is spam.
You didn't have to manually do it, you know, and each and every screen slide film like you.
All right.
So for that, let me start at the moment, we just configure the bashara and later we'll come back and
do this because I want to show you the context in which situation you need to do this.
Until then, we will this week until it's good.
Add context as we have the excuse.
So to configure excuse.
Let me put that just right here.
So.
Excuse, don't default.
Defaults don't base, you are.
So we give this property here, you can set the base here, so base here it is.
You can see here we are using EPA that is coming from config file, so this could be the config.
So we have the yeah, and this is the b0, right?
So we can use that.
So let's go to context.
The important.
Important from.
Config.
OK.
No.
If something happened, you us for him, that would be Indian.
So that's the base year we configure out, this will later we will do more, but at the moment, let's
leave it like this.
Now, once you do this, you can go back here and sign in and you don't have to keep writing the EPA
now.
He can just use less time.
And because this mission has already been set here in the Texas excuse defaults.
So that's the beauty.
You don't have to do that.
You don't have to keep writing the the full path.
The vision you just gave the endpoint.
So that sign in.
Let's go to sign up and let's do the same here.
Perfect.
Now that means freedom in this as we can't, we didn't have to keep importing that point.
OK, let's give it a try.
Give us some issues you can fake.
Import.
That's, you know, I think it is it's good to cross.
Import API from.
Let me take if it is expert default or something else.
One feature, OK, expert cost.
I guess that's right.
Let me give it a reload.
Unable to reach a model.
So that is kind of fake, oh, sorry, configures of fire ready to individual file.
That's right.
Before I was trying to fix this up, that's not right.
This is going to be awesome.
It's brilliant.
All right.
Beautiful.
We got that.
Now let me quickly go to our teams this default route to signing.
Come on.
Was this hardcore, but does more?
To sign in.
Let me sign him, and you can see here, once we sign in, we give this out, we get redirected and
we have the token and his information in this state.
Beautiful.